<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<NotesStructure xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <notes>
    <NoteStructure>
      <noteName>Three Barons</noteName>
      <pages>
        <string>Three barons lived at the top of a tall wooden tower
The first was very small, but enjoyed life slowly and to the fullest
The second was average, indecisive and lived minute to minute
The third was so tall, and the quickest thinker of them all

The barons seldom left home, afraid of the sun
The lot of them had never learned the notion of fun
They lived in total darkness, no light at all
Passers-by claimed they even spoke to their walls

One day, in came a new companion
A little black cat with the pride of a lion
They cherished and loved it and made it their own
But soon it grew hungry and thin to the bone</string>
        <string>“It ran. It ran. The cat ran away.”
The third baron screamed, on that heinous day
They pondered and pondered but urgency grew
They had to move, go out, it's the least they could do

At the strike of three, the first baron left
The light grazed his skin and his legs failed the test
He stood there, frozen, pointing and motionless
The other two stood watching and turning their hands

The second baron followed suit and got further than the first
Four steps to be exact, before his legs suddenly burst
He stood there,  frozen, pointing and motionless
The last remaining baron stood quietly turning his hand</string>
        <string>It took all his courage but the third baron ran
As much as anyone could or anyone can
From the first baron, he made it eight steps in fact
Only to realize he was on a circular track

Three barons lived at the top of a tall wooden tower
The first was very small, but enjoyed life slowly and to the fullest
The second was average, indecisive and lived minute to minute
The third was so tall, and the quickest thinker of them all</string>
      </pages>
    </NoteStructure>
    <NoteStructure>
      <noteName>Wall Plaque</noteName>
      <pages>
        <string>The shadows of the night will guide your line of sight.
		
And if you chance upon a blue moon,
Reflect on your perspective.

The prey must turn its back to the predator,
Only then will the pieces come together.</string>
      </pages>
    </NoteStructure>
  </notes>
</NotesStructure>